Maybe if Yash is with us, we can just
quickly recap, you know, uh two
insurance results, ICA Pro Life and ICA
Lombard, both from the same group. Yash,
take us through what both reported.
Well, um both uh you know, insurance
companies from the house of ICICI
reported their results yesterday just uh
you know with a gap of about half an
hour but the reactions are very diverse
today uh in terms of how the stock price
is moving for ICA potential life. If I
have to describe the results in one
word, weak growth when it comes to the
fourth quarter, but strong margin
performance. Uh the reason why the stock
is higher in trade today, there are
three important reasons. First one, the
margin performance has been very strong.
A on a year-on-year basis as well, the
margins have come stronger. B the
expectation was uh you know lower and
this particular margin performance has
managed to beat that expectation as well
on the positive side. Second reason is
strong management commentary when it
comes to the management coming out and
saying that uh you know they will be
able to outperform the industry average
growth in FI26. Third one is the
positioning itself. The stock was down
14% in the last 3 months. Uh you know
the fear about margins seems to be
non-existent at least as far as the Q4
result is concerned and hence the stock
has sort of you know picked that up and
is moving higher in trade today. for
ICIC Lombard it's a strong Q4 uh you
know when it comes to growth as well as
the underwriting performance but the
reason why the stock is lower or under
pressure today first one the stock has
been flat in the last 3 months so
positioning wise of course it's it's on
the negative side when it comes to you
know the stock moving today or reacting
today second is the uncertainty on the
motor insurance portfolio the biggest
portfolio about 40% off the book but how
will it pan out in FI26 with auto sales
being a little disappoint pointing there
is a lot of uncertainty in terms of how
motor insurance portfolio for ICICI
Lombard will work out. Third reason no
certainty again when it comes to
revision in prices for motor third party
the company and the sector has been
expecting a revision for a few years now
hasn't happened again for FI26 there is
no certainty no word the management also
on the channel said the same thing on
how the prices would be revised in FI26
if they would be revised uh you know at
all and that is also playing on the
stock today.
Thank you very much for